https://www.floridacentercosmetic.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last updated May 26, 2020
Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at Cosmetic Surgery Center of South Florida, doing business as South Florida Center for Cosmetic Surgery (“South Florida Center for Cosmetic Surgery”, “we”, “us”, or “our”).
We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right
to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at info@floridacenter.com.
When you visit our website https://www.floridacentercosmetic.com/, and use our services, you trust us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy policy, we seek to explain to you in the clearest way
possible what information we collect, how we use it and what rights you
have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it
carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy policy that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Sites and our services.
This privacy policy
applies to all information collected through our
website (such as https://www.floridacentercosmetic.com/), and/or any related services, sales, marketing or events (we refer to them collectively in this privacy policy as the “Services“).
Please read this privacy policy carefully as it will help you make informed decisions about sharing your personal information with us.
TABLE OF CONTENTS
1. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
2. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?
3. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?
4. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?
5. WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?
6. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?
7. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?
8. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?
9. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES
10. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?
11. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?
12. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?
1. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT? Personal information you disclose to us
In Short: We collect personal information that you provide to us.
We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when
expressing an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and services, when participating in activities on the Services or otherwise contacting us
.
The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Services, the choices you make and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect can include the following:
Publicly Available Personal Information. We collect first name, maiden name, last name, and nickname; current and former address; email addresses; phone numbers; social media; medical history; and other similar data.
Personal Information Provided by You. We collect data about health, DNA, medical records, FitBit, and similar apps; data held by a hospital or doctor; financial information (credit card number, purchase history, invoices); and other similar data.
All
personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete and
accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal
information.
Information automatically collected
In Short: Some information — such as IP address and/or browser and device characteristics — is collected automatically when you visit our Services.
We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Services.
This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name
or contact information) but may include device and usage information,
such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating
system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country,
location, information about how and when you use our Services and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.
Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.
Online Identifiers. We collect device’s geolocation; devices; applications; tools and protocols, such as IP (Internet Protocol) addresses; cookie identifiers, or others such as the ones used for analytics and marketing;
and other similar data.
2. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?
In Short: We
process your information for purposes based on legitimate business
interests, the fulfillment of our contract with you, compliance with our
legal obligations, and/or your consent.
We use personal information collected via our Services
for a variety of business purposes described below. We process your
personal information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate
business interests, in order to enter into or perform a contract with
you, with your consent, and/or for compliance with our legal
obligations. We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely on next
to each purpose listed below.
We use the information we collect or receive:
To send you marketing and promotional communications.
We and/or our third party marketing partners may use the personal
information you send to us for our marketing purposes, if this is in
accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt-out of our
marketing emails at any time (see the ”
WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS
” below).
To send administrative information to you. We
may use your personal information to send you product, service and new
feature information and/or information about changes to our terms,
conditions, and policies.
Fulfill and manage your orders. We may use your information to fulfill and manage your orders, payments, returns, and exchanges made through the Services.
Deliver targeted advertising to you. We
may use your information to develop and display content and advertising
(and work with third parties who do so) tailored to your interests
and/or location and to measure its effectiveness.
Request Feedback. We may use your information to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Services.
To enforce our terms, conditions and policies for Business Purposes, Legal Reasons and Contractual.
To respond to legal requests and prevent harm. If we receive a subpoena or other legal request, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond.
To manage user accounts. We may use your information for the purposes of managing our account and keeping it in working order.
To deliver services to the user. We may use your information to provide you with the requested service.
To respond to user inquiries/offer support to users.
We may use your information to respond to your inquiries and solve any
potential issues you might have with the use of our Services.
3. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?
In Short: We
only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to
provide you with services, to protect your rights, or to fulfill
business obligations.
We may process or share data based on the following legal basis:
Consent: We may process your data if you have given us specific consent to use your personal information in a specific purpose. Legitimate Interests: We may process your data when it is reasonably necessary to achieve our legitimate business interests. Performance of a Contract: Where we have entered into a contract with you, we may process your personal information to fulfill the terms of our contract. Legal Obligations:
We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so
in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a
judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response
to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public
authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements). Vital Interests:
We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to
investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of
our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to
the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in
litigation in which we are involved.
More specifically, we may need to process your data or share your personal information in the following situations:
Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers.
We may share your data with third party vendors, service providers,
contractors or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and
require access to such information to do that work. Examples include:
payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services,
customer service and marketing efforts. We may allow selected third
parties to use tracking technology on the Services, which will enable them to collect data about how you interact with the Services
over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze
and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better
understand online activity. Unless described in this Policy, we do not
share, sell, rent or trade any of your information with third parties
for their promotional purposes.
Business Transfers.
We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during
negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or
acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
Third-Party Advertisers. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Services.
These companies may use information about your visits to our Website(s)
and other websites that are contained in web cookies and other tracking
technologies in order to provide advertisements about goods and
services of interest to you.
4. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?
In Short: We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information.
We
may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and
pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how
we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set
out in our Cookie Policy.
5. WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?
In Short: We
are not responsible for the safety of any information that you share
with third-party providers who advertise, but are not affiliated with,
our websites.
The Services
may contain advertisements from third parties that are not affiliated
with us and which may link to other websites, online services or mobile
applications. We cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of data you
provide to any third parties. Any data collected by third parties is not
covered by this privacy policy
. We are not responsible
for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any
third parties, including other websites, services or applications that
may be linked to or from the
Services
. You should review the policies of such third parties and contact them directly to respond to your questions.
6. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?
In Short: We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless otherwise required by law.
We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy, unless a longer
retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax,
accounting or other legal requirements). No purpose in this policy will
require us keeping your personal information for longer than 2 years.
When
we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal
information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if this is not
possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored
in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal
information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is
possible.
7. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?
In Short: We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 18 years of age.
We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Services,
you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or
guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of
the Services.
If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of
age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take
reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If
you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age
18, please contact us at info@floridacenter.com.
8. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?
In Short: You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time.
If
you are resident in the European Economic Area and you believe we are
unlawfully processing your personal information, you also have the right
to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority. You
can find their contact details here:
http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm.
Cookies and similar technologies: Most
Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you
can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject
cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could
affect certain features or services of our Services. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Services visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
.
9. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES
Most
web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications
include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to
signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online
browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology
standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been
finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals
or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not
to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that
we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a
revised version of this privacy policy.
10. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?
In Short: Yes, if you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal information.
California
Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law,
permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain
from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of
personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct
marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with
which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding
calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make
such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the
contact information provided below.
If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Services, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Services.
To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact
information provided below, and include the email address associated
with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will
make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.
11. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?
In Short: Yes, we will update this policy as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws.
We may update this privacy policy from time to time. The
updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the
updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we
make material changes to this privacy policy, we may notify you
either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly
sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy policy frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
12. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?
If you have questions or comments about this policy, you may email us at info@floridacenter.com or by post to:
Cosmetic Surgery Center of South Florida
915 Middle River Dr
Suite 213Fort Lauderdale, FL 33304
United States
HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?
Based
on the laws of some countries, you may have the right to request access
to the personal information we collect from you, change that
information, or delete it in some circumstances. To request to review,
update, or delete your personal information, please visit: https://www.floridacentercosmetic.com/contact-us/. We will respond to your request within 30 days.
Contact Us
915 Middle River Dr. #213
Fort Lauderdale, FL 33304
Phone: (954) 565-7575
All Procedures
MedSpa
Fly In Program
Financing
Copyright © 2020 South Florida Center for Cosmetic Surgery. All rights reserved.
Our Current Specials
